Welcome to Zip Text. This video will
demonstrate the application's
functionality for quick calling and
messaging. This is the main screen
showing a contact and a message. Use the
arrows to select a contact to call or a
message to send. The info screen
explains that you can create up to 10
contacts and 10 messages. Hold the
contact button to send a call or select
the down arrow and hold the message to
send a text. To set up the application,
press the gear icon and you will see the
contact settings and text message
settings options. The contact setup
screen displays all saved contacts. You
can remove them using the stop icon, but
remember that you can't have more than
10 contacts. You can import a contact or
add one manually. Preview the contacts
background and click the arrows to
select a different one. Once the contact
is added, you will see it in the contact
setup screen. You can now use the
contact to make a call or send a
message. The message setup screen allows
you to manage the saved messages up to
10 in total. You can remove a message
using the stop icon. You can add a
message by pressing the plus button, but
you can only have 10 messages total in
this setup screen. Just like with
contacts, you can preview the messages
background and click the arrows to
select a different one for the quick
text button. Once you have selected a
contact and a message from the main
screen, a text message is sent
automatically.