This video examines how a genetic
algorithm can be used to evolve better
solutions, in this case, better
surviving fish. We observe four
different generations of the simulation
from generation zero to generation 999.
At generation zero, the simulation
begins. The red fish with the highest
scores have very random traits, and the
top 50% are shown after the rest of the
fish were eaten by sharks. By generation
48, fish size tends to decrease and
speed is very slow. The radius arc and
intelligence are slightly higher
compared to previous generations. At
generation 241, we see a slight increase
in size. Speed remains slow, but turn
frequency is significantly higher and
intelligence is very high. Finally, at
generation 999, the evolved fish are
extremely small, very slow, have a big
radius arc and high intelligence. This
reflects the impact of the genetic
algorithm in selecting optimal traits
for survival.